http://www.eljer.com/legal.aspx

Eljer Online
Be the first to know about promotions & save your favorite products online.
Our Privacy Policy has been updated and is now
available.  It will become effective 30 days from publication.  If
you have any questions, please reach out to us using the information provided
under the “Contacting Us” section below. Please note that specific provisions
of this Privacy Policy may be applicable only to residents of the State of
California.
Last Updated: December 19, 2019
AS America, Inc. d/b/a LIXIL Water Technology
Americas (“LWTA”), is a business unit of the LIXIL Group Corporation, and holds
a leading market position in a key region of the world.  Brands in its
portfolio include American Standard, GROHE and DXV, among others.  LWTA,
of course, recognizes that privacy is of key importance and we want you to be
familiar with how we collect, use and disclose your information.  This
Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of LWTA as well as its
subsidiaries in connection with information that we collect through various
channels including the websites we own and operate (collectively,
the “Websites”), through the software applications made available by us
for use on or through computers and mobile devices (the “Apps”), through
our social media pages that we control (collectively, our “Social Media
Pages”), through email messages and through your communications with us
(collectively, including the Websites, the Apps and our Social Media Pages,
the “Online Services,” and together with offline and sales channels,
the “Services”).  Our Privacy Policy does not govern our collection
of information through any means other than through the Services and it does
not govern the collection of information by any third parties. This Privacy
Policy applies to Websites on which it is found posted.
By using our Websites or Services, or by
providing any information to us, you agree to the terms and conditions of this
Privacy Policy.
Collection of Information
“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to
an identifiable individual.  “Other Information” is any
information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly
relate to an individual.  Personal Information and Other Information is
herein collectively referred to as “Information”.
We may collect Information such as name,
address, telephone number and email address, date of birth, or goods and
services purchased, special requests made, and information about your
preferences and user account, either directly or through third parties.
We may also collect browser and device information, App usage data and
information collected through other technologies, as well as demographic and
aggregated information.
If you submit any Information relating to
other people to us or to our service providers in connection with the Services
(e.g., if you make a purchase or register for another individual), you
represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the
Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
We and our service providers may collect
Information in a variety of ways, including:
Through Our Online Services: We may collect Information when you place an order or otherwise
purchase goods and services from us, communicate with us via online chat
services, inform us of any special requests or preferences you may have,
or sign up for a newsletter or participate in a survey, contest, or promotional
offer.
Through Our Offline Services: We may collect Information from you offline, such as when one of
our representatives visits your home, when you place an order over the
phone or contact customer service.
From Other Sources: We may receive your Information from other sources, such as public
databases, joint marketing partners, and other third parties. This may
include information from your credit card provider, and other partners,
and from social media platforms (including from people with whom you are
friends or otherwise connected to).  Certain Information from your
social media account may be linked to other Online Services and shared
with us, which may include Information that is part of your social media
account or your friends’ account.
From Authorized Licensees: LWTA may from time to time enter into a license or similar
agreement with a third party to sell products and services under a LWTA
brand.  Such an “Authorized Licensee” is independent from LWTA and
may provide information to us about your purchases or your intersection
with its sales or service departments.
Through your browser or device: Certain Information is collected by most browsers or
automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC)
address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution,
operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model,
language, Internet browser type and version and the name and version of
the Online Services (such as the Apps) you are using. We use this
information for business purposes such as ensuring that the Online
Services function properly.
Through your use of the Apps: When you download and use an App, we and our service providers and
business partners may track and collect App usage data, such as the date
and time the App on your device accesses our servers and what information
and files have been downloaded to the App based on your device number.
Payment information: While payment information may be required if you elect to pay for
certain goods or services via credit card, we do not collect and do not
have access to complete credit card numbers.  This information is
passed through directly to our service provider, which processes
payment.  We do not take any responsibility for the acts or website
of the service provider regarding the processing of this
information.  We do retain “masked” or portions of credit card
numbers for limited purposes such as confirmation of credit card payment
receipts.
Using cookies: We collect information through the use of cookies which allows us
to, among other things, tailor our advertisements or offers to you. If you
do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a
simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline
cookies or be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer to
your computer of a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site.
If, however, you do not accept cookies, you may experience some
inconveniences such as needing to log in every time you visit or you may
not receive offers from us that are relevant to your interests and
needs.  At this time, we do not respond to browser “Do-Not-Track”
signals.
Using pixel tags and other similar
technologies: Pixel tags (also known as web
beacons and clear GIFs) may be used in connection with some Online
Services to, among other things, track the actions of users of the Online
Services (including email recipients), measure the success of our
marketing campaigns and compile statistics about usage of the Online
Services and response rates.
Google Analytics: We also use Google Analytics and Adobe Analytics, which use
cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about
use of the Services and report on activities and trends. These services
may collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps and
online resources. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners,
and opt-out by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on,
available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
You can learn more about Adobe and opt-out by visiting http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html.
Using Adobe Flash technology (including
Flash Local Shared Objects (“Flash LSOs”)) and other similar technologies: We may use Flash LSOs and other technologies to, among other
things, collect and store information about your use of the Online
Services. If you do not want Flash LSOs stored on your computer, you can
block Flash LSO storage using the tools contained in the Website
Storage Settings Panel. You can also control
Flash LSOs by going to the Global
Storage Settings Panel and following the
instructions.  Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict
or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality
of some Flash applications, including those used in connection with the
Online Services. For more information, you may also wish to refer to https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html.
IP Address: Your
IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that
you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). An IP address may
be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a
user accesses the Online Services, along with the time of the visit and
the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP addresses is standard
practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and
other services. We use IP addresses for several purposes, such as
calculating usage levels, diagnosing server problems and administering the
Online Services. We may also derive your approximate location from your IP
address.
Physical Location & Mobile
Location-Based Services: We may collect the
general physical location of your device by, for example, using satellite,
cell phone tower, WiFi signals, or other technologies. We may use your
device’s general physical location to provide you with personalized
location-based services, advertising and content.  If you have
downloaded one of our Apps, you may enroll to receive special offers by
agreeing to the use of technologies that enable us to collect information
about your precise location through your mobile device’s Bluetooth or
similar capabilities. We will collect this precise location information
only if you opt-in through the App (either during your initial login or
later) to receive the special offers and by enabling these capabilities on
your mobile device.
By aggregating information: Aggregated Information does not personally identify you or any
other user of the Services (for example, we may aggregate Information to
calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area
code).
Use of Information
We may use and disclose Information for
various purposes, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable
law.  Such purposes include:
To provide the products or services you
request.
To complete your order and provide you with
related customer service.
To receive limited payment information from
the payment processor to validate credit card payment receipts against our
orders.
To send you administrative information,
marketing communications, promotional offers, periodic customer
satisfaction, market research or quality assurance surveys.
To personalize your experience and with
respect to the Online Services by presenting products and offers tailored
to you.
To allow you to participate in sweepstakes,
contests and other promotions and to administer these activities. Some of
these activities have additional rules and may be operated by service
providers who have their own rules, as well.  Please read any such
rules carefully as they could explain how your Information is used and
disclosed.
For our business purposes, such as data
analysis, audits, security and fraud monitoring and prevention, developing
new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Services, identifying
usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns
and operating and expanding our business activities.
We may also use Information in connection with
loyalty programs and/or other expressly subscribed rewards based programs to:
Send you information regarding your account
status and activities;
Assess the benefits to which you are entitled;
Administer points earned;
Manage your choices regarding how you wish
to earn points (e.g., participating airlines and other company loyalty
programs) and track your points and transaction activity.
Disclosure of Information
Your Information may be disclosed in
connection with the following services that we provide as a global company:
Appointments: The Information you provide to us for making an appointment in
your home is made available to the applicable service partner for the
purpose of meeting your appointment request.
Within LIXIL GROUP Corporation
affiliates: We may disclose your Information
to LWTA affiliates such as our parent, subsidiaries and other affiliated
entities within the LIXIL Group Corporation group for the purposes
described in this Privacy Policy, such as for the purpose of sending you
marketing communications, consistent with your choices. You should also be
aware that Information may be transferred to or received by such affiliated
entities in the U.S. or in other countries, which may have different
privacy regulations than those applicable in the country where you
reside.
To Service Providers: We may disclose Information to our third party service providers
and partners who provide services such as advertising and media, website
hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, information
technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email
delivery, auditing and other services.  Our Websites may sometimes
contain links to other service provider websites.  We assume no
responsibility for the content or the privacy policies and practices on
those websites.
To Authorized Licensees: We may disclose your Information to an Authorized Licensee in
connection with the Services.  An example of this is a dealer or
retailer that offers our products for sale.  The third-party dealer
or retailer may contact you directly by email, phone or postal mail.
Information you provide to them will be subject to the privacy policy of
that Authorized Licensee and not to this Privacy Policy.
Sponsors of Sweepstakes, Contests and
other Promotions.  We may operate
sweepstakes, contests and other promotions through the Services that may
require online registration with us or with third-party providers of such
contests or promotions.  You should carefully review the rules of
each sweepstakes, contest or promotion in which you participate through
the Services, as they may contain additional information about the
third-party provider’s use or disclosure of your Information.  If
there is a conflict in the treatment of Information between the rules of
the sweepstakes or other promotion and this Policy, the terms and
conditions of such rules control.
Through Social Media: We may disclose your Information to your friends associated with
your social media account, to other website users and to your social media
account provider, in connection with your social sharing activity.
By linking your Online Services account and your social media account, you
authorize us to share information with your social media account provider,
and you understand that the use of the information we share will be
governed by the social media site’s privacy policy and according to the
privacy settings you have chosen.  In addition, when you elect to
post information on message boards, chat, profile pages and blogs and
other services to which you are able to post information and materials
(including, without limitation, our Social Media Pages) any such information
you post or disclose through these services will become public and may be
available to other users and the general public.
Corporate Reorganization: We may disclose your Information to a third party in the event of
any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or
other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock
(including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
We may also use and disclose Information as we
believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) to comply with applicable law, which
may include laws from outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with
legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government
authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country
of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our
operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights,
privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and
(g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may
sustain.
Third Party Services: This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not
responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third
parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which
the Services link, third party payment services, or any third-party
website. The inclusion of a link on the Online Services does not imply our
endorsement. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, this
third party’s collection, use and disclosure of your Information.
In addition, we are not responsible for the
information collection, use, disclosure or security policies or practices of
other organizations, such as, but not limited to Facebook, Apple, Google,
Microsoft, RIM or any other app developer or social media platform provider.
Sale of Information
California residents, your Information may be sold or shared in connection with following commercial
interests we have as a global company:
Buying, selling, renting, leasing, sharing for commercial purposes, subscribing of information for economic benefit or other consideration;
Exchanging products, goods, property, services or information for economic benefit or other consideration; or
To enable a commercial transaction, including but not limited to the sale or acquisition of a company, a merger, or a change in control of Lixil Group Corporation.
Interest Based Advertising
We use a variety of tracking
technologies.  We collect information about users over time and across
different sites when you use these sites. We collect this information using a
variety of tracking tools including but not limited to cookies, beacons,
pixels, tags, statistical IDs, mobile advertising IDs, flash cookies, and
similar technologies. We display interest-based using information gathered
about you over time across multiple Sites, including mobile apps.
Our interest-based ads may be served to you on
our Websites, in emails, or on third-party Sites. These ads may be served by us
or by third parties . The ads might be about us or about other companies’
products or services.
You Can Opt-Out of Some Interest-Based
Advertising. There are various ways to opt-out of interest-based advertising.
The Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising provides
consumers with the ability to opt-out of having their online behavior used for
interest-based advertising using third party cookies. If you want to opt out of
this online behavioral advertising, visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ and http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.  This will opt you out of many –but not all- of the interest-based
advertising activities in which we or third parties engage.  The Digital
Advertising Alliance offers a tool for opting out of the collection of
information across mobile devices for interest based advertising. To opt-out of
this cross-device interest based advertising from companies participating in
this tool, download the AppChoices app at http://youradchoices.com/appchoices.
Security
We seek to use reasonable technical and
administrative measures to protect Information within our organization.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet or storage system can be
guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction
with us is no longer secure or has been compromised, please immediately notify
us at via our toll-free number 1- 800-442-1902,
by email at optout@lixil.com, or regular mail, Attn: Sr. Director Customer Care, 1 Centennial
Avenue, Piscataway, NJ 08854.
Your Choices
If you no longer want to receive
marketing-related emails from us, you may opt-out by following the instructions
in any such email you receive from us.  In addition, you can also opt-out
from communications by emailing optout@lixil.com or sending regular mail to
Attn: Sr. Director Customer Care, 1 Centennial Avenue, Piscataway, NJ 08854.
We will try to comply with your request(s) as
soon as reasonably practicable.  Please note that if you opt-out of
receiving marketing-related emails from us, we may still send you important
administrative messages, from which you cannot opt-out.
Accessing, changing or suppressing Personal Information:
If you would like to review, correct or update Personal Information that you
have previously provided to us, you may contact us at optout@lixil.com or sending regular mail to Attn: Sr. Director Customer Care, 1
Centennial Avenue, Piscataway, NJ 08854.
In your request, please make clear what
Personal Information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to
have your Personal Information suppressed from our database, or other
limitations you would like to put on our use of your Personal
Information.  We may only implement requests with respect to the Personal
Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send
us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing
your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably
practicable.
Special Notice for
California Residents:
Individual customers who reside in California,
and whose Personal Information we have collected, disclosed, or sold, may acquire
certain rights regarding their Personal Information, including the right of
access, the right to deletion, the right to opt-out of the sale of your
Personal Information, and the right to not be discriminated against.
California Resident’s Right of Access
Your right of access allows you to request certain
information about your Personal Information we are collecting, disclosing for a
business purpose, or selling, which may include affiliates within the LIXIL Group
Corporation.  The information you are entitled to will depend on the
specific actions that we take with your Personal Information.  Please note, in
addition to other forms of Personal Information, we may perform the following
actions on the categories of data disclosed below:
Collect
Disclose
Sell
Name and address
Name and address
Name and address
Electronic mail address
Credit Card
As a California resident you may request that
we delete your Personal Information and we must comply with any such request.  However,
there may be certain circumstances where we are legally required, or permitted,
to retain such Personal Information.  In the event that we are required to retain
your Personal Information, we will continue to protect it as provided herein.  It
is your right to not be discriminated against, for exercising any of these
California-based rights and LIXIL Group Corporation will not deny you goods or
services, change the prices or fees that you are charged, provide a different
quality of good or service, suggest any of the preceding if it is your
intention to exercise any of the California based rights herein
California Resident’s Right to Opt-out
A California resident’s right to opt-out is
unique in that it only applies to Personal Information that we are selling, if
any.  You may submit any request to exercise one of these rights via our
toll-free number 1- 800-442-1902, by
email at optout@lixil.com, or regular mail, Attn: Sr. Director Customer Care, 1 Centennial
Avenue, Piscataway, NJ 08854. In addition, if you wish to opt out of the
sale of your Personal Information, you may do so via this link “DO NOT SELL MY INFORMATION.” Please note,
opting-out is not permanent, and you can change your mind at any time.  If
after 12 months from opting out, we may follow up with you to see if you would
like to opt back in.
Within forty-five days of receiving a
California resident’s opt-out request, we will provide a list of activities
related to the collection, disclosure or sale of your Personal Information during
the immediately preceding twelve (12) month period. If your request is not made
from the specific email address or phone number associated with the Personal
Information over which you seek to exercise your rights, we must be able to
readily verify your identity before acting on any requests submitted and may
extend beyond the forty-five day period.  Such requests may be made no more
than twice per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests
submitted by methods other than as specified and provided for in this section.
Special Notice for European
Residents:
For users residing in the European Economic Area (“EEA”),
this Privacy Policy is subject to the provisions of the General Data Protection
Regulation ("GDPR") and other applicable privacy laws.  Under
the GDPR, Lixil Group Corporation is a data “Controller” and you are a “Data
Subject” with certain protected privacy rights concerning your personal
data.  Lixil Group Corporation will take commercially reasonable steps to
maintain compliance with GDPR requirements.  We will process your personal data
in accordance with your explicit consent (by using the Services, you hereby
consent to our processing), to fulfill a contract, as required to conduct our
business and pursue our legitimate interests, and to respond to legal requests
by government entities.  Your data is not used to make automated decisions.  We
will store and hold data collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy
outside of the EEA, and will process it outside of the EEA.  When Lixil Group Corporation
processes the data of EEA residents outside of the EEA, when required under the
GDPR, we will implement the mandatory safeguards and/or mechanisms in relation
to the transfer.
Special rights of EEA Residents
Individual customers who reside in the EEA,
and whose Personal Information we have access to or control of, may acquire
certain rights regarding their Personal Information, including the right of
access, the right to correction, the right to be forgotten, the right to suspend/restrict
processing, the right of data portability, the right to object to processing,
and the right to not be subject to automated decision-making or profiling,
though we do not engage in such automated decision-making or profiling.
Retention: Please
note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes
and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting a change
or deletion.  There may also be residual information that will remain
within our databases and other records, which will not be removed. In addition,
there may be certain information that we are unable to enable you to review,
for legal, security, or other reasons.
We will retain your Information for the period necessary to fulfill the
purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is
required or permitted by law.
Use of Services by Minors
The Services are not directed to individuals
under the age of eighteen (18), and we request that they not provide Personal
Information through the Services.
Cross-Border Transfer
LIXIL Water Technology is a global
organization and provides a global service. Sharing information cross border is
at times essential to the Services. As a result, we may, subject to applicable
law, transfer Information collected in connection with the Services, to these
entities in countries where information protection standards may differ from
those in the country where you reside. By using our Services and Websites, you
agree that we may transfer your Information globally and process it or store it
on equipment located in other countries outside the country where you reside in
line with the above-referenced policies.
Updates to This Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy. The “Last
Updated” legend at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy
was last revised. Your use of the Services following any changes means that you
accept the updated Privacy Policy.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy
Policy please contact us at optout@lixil.com or sending regular mail to
Attn: Sr. Director Customer Care, 1 Centennial Avenue, Piscataway, NJ 08854.
Please do not include credit card or other sensitive information in your emails
to us since email communications are not always secure.
Feel free to contact us anytime you'd like. American Standard experts are standing by. Our customer service phone number is listed here along with our hours of service. Drop us a line.
Contact Us Online
Call Customer Service
800-442-1902
Monday through Friday
8:00 AM to 7:00 PM ET
Saturday
10:00 AM to 4:00 PM ET
Write Customer Service
